so surface area is as if we were
painting the whole thing how much area
is that so we're gonna add up the area
of all six sides
this front side is two by five so it has
an area of ten and we also have the back
side that matches this that we can't see
we'd say two times this 10
plus this top is also 2 by 5 so it's
also 10 and then we also have the bottom
so we're gonna multiply that by two then
we have this side here which is two by
two
area four and then we have it on the
other side over there so there's two of
those
so we have the front and back top and
bottom and the two sides 2 times 10 is
20 2 times 10 is 20
and 2 times 4 is 8. 20 plus 20 plus 8 is
they don't give us a label anywhere so
we can just call this unit
squared and 48 units squared is the
answer to the question if you have any
other math
questions check out andymath.com or
comment below on what you'd like me to
do next
i'll talk to you soon bye